Hello.
こんにちは
How are you?
お元気ですか?
I'm fine.
元気ですよ
fine?
元気?
Yeah, that's good.
そうか、よかった
I'm fine too.
俺も元気なんですよ
It's hot every day if I don't go home.
お帰りなきゃ毎日熱いですけどね
It's hot.
熱いですね
Aren't you going home?
お帰りないですか?
How have you been lately?
最近どうなの?
Seriously?
真面目に?
I'm serious, always.
真面目にやってますよ、いつも
Are you doing it?
やってる?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, uncle too, please conserve your strength for a while.
じゃあ ね、おじさんもね、ちょっとおじさんに体力を温存して
Will you?
ます か?
So that's it.
ということでね
Well, I have a request for you today.
じゃあ、ちょっと今日はお願いがあるんですけど、
Have you ever wanted to bully a man?
男の人をいじめたいことはありますか?
There's no need to bully me.
いじめるのはないですよ
do not have?
ない?
Yeah.
うん
But it looks perfect, you know?
でもなんか完全に見た目が、ほら、
Won't it look like S?
Sっぽく見られたりしない?
Yeah, but I'm not really that serious.
えー、でもなんかそんなガチなやつはないですよ
Is that so?
そうなの?
Do you ever get approached by someone who looks a bit like a masochist?
なんかちょっとMっぽいとかの人が近づいてきたりとかしない?
Ah, there are some people like that,
あー、なんかそういう人もいるんですけど、
I don't know what to do.
何でやったらいいかわからなくて
Yeah.
うん
In the end, it seems like it ends in a vague way.
結局なんか曖昧な感じで終わるみたいな
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I see.
そっかー
Well, you know, I'm still young.
ま、でもね、まだ若いから
As I get older, I start seducing men, etc.
こっから年取ってくるとね、こう男の人をたぶらかしたりとかね、
I have to do it in Terentekuda.
テレンテクダでね、しなきゃいけないんですよ
Yeah.
うん
yes.
はい
Well, it's been a while since I've talked about a lot of things today.
じゃあ、ちょっと今日はね、いろんなことちょっとまた久しぶり
So, while I was doing that, for a while,
なので、 あれしていきながら、ちょっとね、
I want you to tease me a little,
ちょっとおじさんいじめてほしいんで、
I'm thinking of letting you bully me.
いじめてもらおうかと思ってんですよ
Yeah, bullying, you understand?
うん、いじめる、わかります?
bully.
いじめる
All you have to do is bully them.
いじめるをすればいいんだよね
Oh yeah, bullying.
そうそう、いじめる
Yeah, well, I think it's easy.
うん、まあ、簡単に考えてるね
Well then, first of all, I...
じゃあね、まず、ね、 ちょっと僕、
I'm coming here, I'm coming next to you,
ここに来ますから、横に来ますから、
Hey, do you understand?
ね、 わかります?
Hey uncle, uncle, are you here?
ちょっと、おじさん、おじさん、ここでしょ?
I'll lend you this.
これ貸してあげるから
So, uncle, can you tease me about this?
じゃあ、これ、おじさん、いじめてあげる?
Yeah.
うん
Suddenly?
いきなり?
picture?
え?
why?
なんで?
Ah, but I've done this before.
あ、でもこれ、やったことあるよ
This?
これを?
Yeah.
うん
Ah.
あぁ
Oh, what is it?
あ、なんだろう?
why?
なんで?
Why are you laughing?
なんで笑う?
Why, why?
なんで、なんであんだろう?
No, I thought it was coming from below.
いや、なんか、こう、下からかなと思って
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Ah.
あぁ
Have you done much?
あんまりやったことあんの?
If you're a man.
男の人なら
do not have.
ない
There isn't.
ないよ
Eh, I guess that's the case with me too?
え、自分もあんだろう?
What have you done?
やったことあんの?
No, no, no.
ない、ない、ない
Is there a sex group like that?
あのセックス組みある?
Well, it looks like it's going to leak some poop, isn't it?
えー、なんかさ、あの、うんちが漏れそうじゃん?
There?
そこ?
What's that there?
そこなんだ?
There.
そこ
Oh, it doesn't hurt or anything?
あ、痛いとかじゃなくて?
Ah, I see.
あ、なるほどね
Even if it hurts, I know when it will feel better.
痛いところも、いつで気持ちよくなるっていうことは分かって
I did.
んだ
Well, I mean, anal...
え、 なんか、だってさ、アナルをさ、
It will be expanded with sex groups,
セックス組みで拡張していくじゃん、
More and more.
どんどん
After all, if you go too far, it'll leak, right?
あれだって、行き過ぎたらさ、うんく漏れるんじゃん、
That's what I thought.
と思って
That part won't leak any more.
そこはもう、そん時では漏れませんけどね
That's what I'm worried about.
それが心配なんだ
yes.
そう
Even though I'm worried like this, if it's an uncle first,
こうやって心配してるのに、最初におじさんなんだら、
Pick up the phone.
電話当てるんだ
That's really interesting.
すっごい興味津々なんだね
Have you ever had a boyfriend like this?
こういう彼氏なかった?
Well, I didn't.
えー、しなかった
A boyfriend you always want.
いつにでも欲しいって彼氏
Well, there were a lot of weird people.
えー、なんかエスな人が多かった
Are there many sexy people?
エスな人多い?
Yeah.
うん
Get more depressed.
もっとうじめって
Did you make it stronger?
強くした?
Yeah.
うん
Wait, what was that?
ちょっと、何だったか
Step on my dick with your foot.
おちんちんをさ、足で踏んで
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
Do this for a moment.
ちょっとこうしてって
copper?
どう?
This kind of uncle.
こういうおじさん
Hmm.
うーん
I said.
俺 と言った
No impressions.
感想なし
Ah, like this.
あ、こんなんで
You're looking down on me.
見下してんのよ
Yeah, but it feels good.
え、でも気持ちいいよ
Isn't there a place where you are stepping on it?
踏んでくれてるとこない?
picture?
え?
Isn't there a place where you are stepping on it?
踏んでくれてるとこない?
Oh, I didn't step on it though.
あ、なんか、踏んではないけどな
There are things like feet.
足的とかがある
be?
ある?
Basically, when I was told to do it and got paid to do it,
足的、やってって言われて、やってお金もらったら、
I feel lucky.
ラッキーとか思うんだ
yes.
そう
I'm glad it was just my feet.
足 でよかったんだって
hey
ね
picture.
え
Would you like to take a look at my pants?
ちょっと パンツ見るか
Just take it off, take it off, take off your pants.
ちょっと脱がして、脱がして、パンツ
Ah, ah, you're standing.
あ、あ、立ってるじゃん
why?
なんで?
I'm standing.
立ってるよ
Yeah.
うん
Hey.
ねえ
Oh, I'm standing.
あ、立ってる
More damp.
もっとうじめて
Stand there.
そこに立って
yes.
そう
Okay.
いいよ
Below, look.
下に、ほら
Usan, turn it.
うさん、回して
Down, down, down, down.
下、下に、下に、下に
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうそう
So with your feet, see.
それで足で、ほら
From above.
上から
a.
あ
Ah, yes, yes.
あ、そうそうそう
a.
あ
It's delicious.
うまいじゃん
Are you making fun of me?
バカにしてる?
Okay.
いいよ
Sit down and see.
座ってほら
Sit down.
座って
What the hell?
なんてこと?
what?
なに?
I really want to be friends with you.
どうしても俺、仲良くしてみたいもんね
hey
ね
picture.
え
After a while, I asked her to give me a footjob, and she said,
俺 が少ししたら、足こきしてって言ったら、
Sit on that side and rub your feet.
その側に座って足こきしてほら
yes.
はい
Rub your feet, rub your feet.
足こきして、足こきして
Yeah.
うん
Oh my god, it feels so good.
やばい、気持ちいい
I've done this before.
これ、やったことあるんだ
これ、やったことあるんだよ
Yeah.
うん
Oh, is there?
あ、あるの?
ah.
あー
Then.
そんで
This is what made people so hard.
こんなんで、キンキン硬くなった人
It's lame.
ダサい
Is it lame?
ダサい?
Why did you say that?
なんで言った?
After doing a little bit, she said she was tired.
少しやったら、疲れたって言って、
Yeah.
うん
I told her that I didn't have to touch her legs so I could tease her comfortably.
足やらなくてもいいから、気持ちよくいじめてって言って、
My penis is stretched out, squeezed in my hands,
おちんちん、どれかけたり、手でしぼえたり、
Lick it, lick it all over,
舐めたり、 全身ちょっと舐めたり、
It feels like I'm teasing you, that's about it.
いじめてるような感じの、それくらいしようか
yes.
はい
So please do a little bit.
そっからね、少しやってくださいね
Do it for about 5 seconds.
5秒くらいやってからね
Yeah.
うん
tired.
疲れた
Are you tired?
疲れちゃった?
Yeah.
うん
Others, you know, bully me.
他の方、ほら、いじめて
Oh, that's good.
ああ、良かったね
ah.
ああ
After doing it for a while, what else feels good other than your penis?
少しやったら、おちんちん以外のどこが気持ちいいの?
While saying such things, I touched on this area a little.
とか言いながら、 こう いう、なんかちょっとこの辺とか触
Like, it's tickling.
って、 ようがくすぐったりとか、
Oh, stop it!
ああ、やめて!
It's like I'm just going to keep doing things while saying things like that.
とか言いながら、 ちょっと、 どんどんやっていくみたいな
What else feels good other than your penis?
おちんちん以外のどこが気持ちいいの?
secret.
秘密
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
secret.
秘密
ah.
ああ
I can't breathe.
息ができない
For a while
しばら
Ku.
く
Armpit?
わ き腹?
Side and belly?
わきわき腹?
Not disciplined?
しつけない?
Uya.
うや
Erotic.
えろ
Wrinkled belly?
しわき腹?
ah.
ああ
Oh, why is that?
ああ、なんでそんな
What, do you want to come in?
え、入れたいの?
He said he wanted to come in.
入 れ たい って 言 うから
When I said I wanted to enter.
入 れたいって言ったら
Well then, I'll go and have a look.
じゃあ、いってみるから
Tell me to lick your belly.
こっちに、お腹を舐めてって言って
Well, let's sit down.
で、で座ろうか
Ah, so many things.
あ、いろいしい
Ahahaha.
あははは
Let's sit down.
座ろう
Looks like it's going to be hot.
おしみそがいそう
Ah, so many things.
あ、いろいしい
What, do you want to come in?
え、入れたいの?
Get some sleep, Pitch.
ちょっと 寝て、ピッチ
Okay, but please drink my pussy first...
じゃあ いいけど、先におまんこをいっぱい飲めて...
Pussy??
おまんこ??
Yeah.
うん
Sitting here?
ここに座の?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, then I went.
あっ、じゃあ行った
There are plenty.
いっぱいがあります
Please, please.
どうかもう
Ah, ah.
ああっ、ああっ
That's good.
よくなぁ
Stop it.
やめろ
Ah.
あぁ ー
Yocchi?
よっち?
yes.
はい
Yeah?
うん?
cormorant
う
Hmmm
ーん うーん
Shall we go?
行 っちゃう?
行っちゃう?
Shall we go?
Did you go?
行 き ました?
Have you gone?
行っちゃった?
What a great pussy. How are you guessing now?
えらいまんこだ どうやって今当ててるの?
Show me, show me, I bought the pussy that went away, come on, come on.
見せて見せて 行っちゃったまんこも買ったし さあさあ、
yes
はい
Will you have it?
持 ってくれるの?
持ってくれるの?
Is it okay?
いい の?
いいの?
Fix it, fix it
直してよ直して
That's terrible, this is a terrible feeling, ah
それ やばい これやばい気持ち あー
This is dangerous, this is dangerous
これ やばいよやばいよ
Is it okay to worry about my bag?
心 配ついて バックでいいの?
It's amazing, it's so kind, it's funny
すごいよ 優しい、おしろ
Hey, push it down a little more, it's about time.
い もうちょっと押し下げて そろそろそ
I'm about to get bored
ろ そろ つまるよ
You're alone, right? But it depends on the person. Are there really people who don't go?
ひ とりでしょ いやでも人によるよ いかない人は本当にいか
No, I've given up already.
ない もう我慢したんだよ
Sorry, I'm gone.
す いません、行っちゃいました
Okay, I held back, so I ended up going to that station on the plane a lot.
よし 我慢したから いっぱい出ちゃった あの機上の駅に
I was about to go for a while, so I held back and came out a lot.
ちょっと 行きそうになってたんで 我慢したんで いっぱい出
I'm sorry, but what should I do if I edit it?
ちゃ いました そ こもすいません 編集したらどうしますかね
Eh, what should I do? Can I name it for now?
えー どうしよう とりあえず俺が名前つけていい?
What should I wear?
なんてつける?
Hmm, what should I do? I'll try not to give up.
う ーん どうしようか 引きたぎらないようにするよ ちょっと
I'm full. This is terrible, but I guess
お 腹いっぱいいっちゃいましたね やばいねこれ でも たぶん
I'll definitely make it a rainbow
絶 対に虹にしますよ
Sorry, are you angry?
す いません 怒ってる?
I'm glad I'm not angry. Things like that happen.
怒ってない よかった そういうことはあるんだね
I don't know if I've woken up to M, but I think it's good.
なんか ちょっと 俺Mに目覚めたか分かんないです いいと思う
If it were okay to go at a higher rank, it wouldn't be this easy.
機 上位で行っていいんだったら こんな楽なくなる感じはない
Right, sorry, thank you. It was fun.
よね すいませんでした、ありがとうございます 楽しかったです
I was happy
幸 せでした